hashdoc.com 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Hashdoc

Hashdoc was created not only to provide a platform for sharing and discovering documents, but to connect professionals and promote individuals and organizations that are sources of high-quality content. In order to provide these services, we must inform you that use of a Hashdoc account or Hashdoc services constitutes an agreement to the use of personal information as permitted in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. 

When you read or download documents from Hashdoc, we collect limited, anonymous data, such as your IP address, web browser, and the URLs of sites from which you come to or leave the Hashdoc website. We use this data to compile statistics and monitor site activity in order to improve the site for our visitors and users. 

By creating an account with Hashdoc, you voluntarily provide us with information, including personally identifiable information, including the following: your name, email address, preferred user name, and password. Without this information, you may not create an account on Hashdoc. We use this information in order to enable you to communicate with other users and interact with the site, to administer your account and customize the service that we provide you (and other users) with, and to send you service-related or promotional emails or communications through the Hashdoc website. We also use cookies to store login information for registered users. 

Please be advised that communications between you and Hashdoc may pass through many machines, programs, browsers, Web servers, networks, or other devices. Some of these devices may create logs of your activities that are recorded on computer systems. 

Hashdoc is not responsible for breaches of privacy that may result from a user's failure secure their data or computer at public workstations and networks, or their passwords and login data. You are responsible for keeping your login information secret and for controlling access to your email communications at all times. Hashdoc is also not responsible for breaches of privacy that may occur as a result of third party access, over which we have no control. 

We retain the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at our sole discretion.
